# Luís Felipe Picareli

lfpicareli@gmail.com +351 917353596

14/10/1993

Lisbon, Portugal

Video Game developer working with **Unity** engine since 2012, proficient with **C#** and working knowledge of a few other languages. Able to code any area related to a video game from gameplay to technical systems, test, debug and create full documentation.

Main Skills Unity, C#, Game Development

## Work Experience

## **Game Developer** • August 2020 → Current

Prime Cut Games · Lisbon

Project planning, mentorship, game programming and development of the title **Zealot** in the **Unity** engine.

Gameplay Programming: Combat and Movement System.

UI Programming: Main Menu and Player HUD.

Systems: Dialogue, Camera, Save Game, Localization and Input.

Unity, C#

## **Software Developer •** November 2016 → August 2018

Addon - Digital Media, Lda · Lisbon

Development of an interactive directory for shopping malls in **Unity** for **Linux** systems.

Unity, C#, Web Development, Linux

#### Unity Developer • May 2012 → July 2016

Universidade Lusófona · Lisbon

Development of a **Serious Game** that served as a platform for cognitive training and rehabilitation, for **Windows**, **WebGL** and **Android**, with integration of **Kinect** and **Google VR**.

Unity, JavaScript, Android, VR, Kinect

#### IT Technician Intern • May 2010 → July 2010

Faculdade de Psicologia da Universidade de Lisboa · Lisbon

Installation and maintenance of software and computer equipment.

IT Support, Computer Maintenance

#### Skills

## **Programming Languages**

Proficient with C#, good knowledge of Javascript, past experience with Java and C, learning Python for a personal project.

Mastery of coding best practices, with great ability to create well organised and readable code.

#### Software

Working with the **Unity** engine since version 3.5, experience with **Git** and **Plastic SCM** (now **Unity VCS**) for version control.

Able to create and manage databases in SQL. Familiar with both Windows and Linux CLI.

Using Blender for personal projects and game modding.

#### Personal

Organised, problem solver, always looking to improve and learn.

Languages Portuguese (Native), English

## Education

## Multimedia Applications and Video Games • EQF 6

Universidade Lusófona · Lisbon

2014 - 2016

Bachelor level course for video game development and multimedia production. **Main Units:** Object Oriented Programming, 3D Modelling, Game Design.

Unity, C#, Java, Javascript, Maya

## **Software Development and Systems Administration** • EQF 5

Universidade Lusófona · Lisbon

2011 – 2012

Comprehensive course with focus on software development.

Main Units: Programming, Software Engineering, Databases, Web Development, Project Management, and Network Architecture and Protocols.

Javascript, C, PHP, SQL

#### **Computer Maintenance** • EQF 4

Escola Secundária de Fonseca Benevides · Lisbon

2007 – 2010

Professional course focused on computer maintenance and repair.

IT Support, Linux, Pascal